<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on Georgia Mountain Haven</title>
    <link>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on Georgia Mountain Haven</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://georgiamountainhaven.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Classes</title>
      <link>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:12:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/classes/</guid>
      <description>Classes are available to anyone; require zoom to join. Saturday To-Shin Do is in person with zoom as an alternative, depending on weather and health conditions.
Please consult your personal physician before beginning any workout practice, including yoga.
Yoga A hatha yoga based class. Typically involves sun salutation variations. A mix of standing, balance, and seated poses and some sequences. Followed by a short ten minute seated meditation period, sometimes focusing on the breath and sometimes with a guided component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:04:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday     09:00 Yoga/Meditation  Yoga/Meditation   To-Shin Do    10:00                     12:15 Fitness Fitness Fitness Fitness Yoga               18:30  To-Shin Do         All classes are over zoom except the Saturday 9am To-Shin Do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/about/</guid>
      <description>About A place to study and grow, to find your path in the world. For questioners, seeking a path toward answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toshindo</title>
      <link>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/toshindo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://georgiamountainhaven.org/toshindo/</guid>
      <description>To-Shin Do Toshindo is the martial art lead by Anshu Mr. and Mrs. Hayes.
It is a self defense art with a philosophy of protection and reaching your own potential.
Our local group trains once a week at the farm and uses zoom as a back up to in person training. Zoom has been helpful not only during the pandemic but also when the weather prohibitted travel or when guests were visiting, to save travel time, or when someone is sick and avoiding spreading their virus to others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
